Appl number 38 is the everything library
so here in in many other cities there is
a - a library where you can go and you I
think you pay a yearly fee here it works
different in different cities and so you
don't have to go and buy a power drill
if you just need to use it once a year
you just go and get it
for a certain period of time and use it
and that can be done on a larger scale
now you do need space to have that but
if you have people who share I think
this is one of the ideas that other
people of cloth with but with the Yelp
for websites and get old direct traffic
there we can always utilize those that
already available to be able to crowd
sourcing crowd share equipment that we
don't all need to buy and so we can be
more efficient with our resources and
money so that is idea number Apple
number 38 everything library